Luyuan He (Allen)

0482052293 | luyuan@hey.com | Github | Sydney, NSW

Summary

3 plus years of experience in automation testing and proficiency in automation testing tools such as Appium/Selenium, combined with extensive experience in software development and excellent communication skills. I am a unique candidate who can fit in and collaborate with other members quickly to improve the quality of your software products.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python, SQL, Javascript, HTML/CSS

Frameworks: Appium/Selenium, Python Unittest, Pytest, Cypress, Django, Bootstrap

Developer Tools: Postman, Jenkins, AWS, Git, Docker

Work Experience

Software Engineer in Test

May 2018 – January 2019

Shanghai, China

Shanghai Rising Digital

- Built and maintained an automation testing framework using Appium, Python Unittest and Page Object Model
- \bullet Wrote and added in-depth test cases for functional and regression testing that covered 96% of the test scenarios
- $\bullet\,$ Saved 5 minutes per test case on average compared to manual testing
- Documented defects found on a defect tracking system and provided constructive feedback
- Participated in troubleshooting issues to drive towards root cause identification and resolution
- Collaborated closely with the developer team under a scrum environment

Software Engineer in Test

April 2016 - May 2018

Lenovo Mobile Communication Technology Shanghai, China
• Created and maintained an automation testing platform for performance and system testing on Android

- Used Git to continuous integrate new performance requirements into the framework
- Reported results against agreed performance metrics and escalate any deviations to management
- Reduced more than 90% of testing time compared to manual testing
- Performed production incident analysis and resolution
- Ensured the successful deployment of products into the market

Software Engineer

July 2015 – April 2016

Shanghai, China

- Implemented web crawlers to search and parse valuable data into company's database using Groovy and Python.
- Worked pro-actively to gauge the performance of the database and wrote scripts to achieve the optimal results
 Designed and managed the company's MongoDB database

Android Developer

August 2014 – June 2015

Shanghai, China

Binpit Information Technology

Gujia Network Science and Technology

- Developed an Android photo editing and sharing application using Java
- Debugged and updated the company's other Android applications
- Maintained and updated the company's website

Projects

<u>FilmFinder</u> | Python, Django, SQLite, Javascript, HTML/CSS, Bootstrap

September 2020 – December 2020

- Developed a web application where users could browse, search for, rate and review movies including features like movie watch lists and movie recommendations using Django with Bootstrap as the front-end
- Used Scrum framework to practice agile development in JIRA
- Used SQLite for data storage and Javascript for creating dynamic web pages

CERTIFICATIONS

Scored 91/100: <u>IKM Software Quality Assurance exam</u> Certificate of Completion: AWS Technical Essentials Day April 2021

September 2019

EDUCATION

University of New South Wales Master of Information Technology Mississippi State University Bachelor of Computer Science Sydney, NSW

March 2019 – January 2021

Starkville, MS, U.S.

July 2009 – December 2013